Guide to the Andrew Smith Gallery Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Andrew Smith Gallery records
1974-2013
WA MSS S-3056
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
678
(678 boxes) + 1 broadside
Andrew Smith, Inc
Scope and Contents
Business records, publications, catalogs, promotional ephemera, printed material, photographs, electronic media, and other papers by or relating to the Andrew Smith Gallery, Inc.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Andrew Smith Gallery, Inc. on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2014.
November 2013 Acquisition: Gift of Andrew Smith, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Boxes 625-640 (financial records): Restricted until January 1, 2040. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Boxes 641-645 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 646-661 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photographs; Andrew Smith, Inc
- November 2013 Acquisition, 1905-1911; 0.25; (1 box)
  - Charles Lummis cyanotypes with related correspondence, 1905-1911 (Box 1)
- February 2014 Acquisition
  - Business and financial records, Series I
    - Financial records
      - Business files, 1964-2011 (Box 2)
      - Business files, 1994-2011 (Box 3)
      - Business files, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
      - Sales commissions, 1988-1993 (Box 5)
      - Business files, 1985 (Box 6)
      - Business files, 1985 (Box 7)
      - Business files, 1992-2007 (Box 8)
      - Payroll and operating expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
      - Invoices, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
      - Operating files, undated (Box 11)
      - Checks and bank statements, 1992-1993 (Box 12)
      - Checks and bank statements, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
      - Purchasing, 1990-1991 (Box 14)
      - Banking files, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
      - Sales and invoices, 1992-1993 (Box 16)
      - Checks and payroll, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
      - Sales commissions, 1991-1992 (Box 18)
      - Sales commissions, 1992-1993 (Box 19)
      - Sales commissions, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Banking and Payroll, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
      - Banking and Payroll, 1992-1994 (Box 22)
      - Banking and Payroll, 1992-1994 (Box 23)
      - Sales and invoices, 1994-1996 (Box 24)
      - Banking files, 1990-1991 (Box 25)
      - Banking files, 1990-1991 (Box 26)
      - Operating accounts, 1995-1997 (Box 27)
      - Banking files, 1996-1999 (Box 28)
      - Banking files, 1996-1999 (Box 29)
      - Sales, invoices, and receipts, 1993-1997 (Box 30)
      - Sales commissions, 1995-1996 (Box 31)
      - Invoices, 1996-1997 (Box 32)
      - Operating bills, 1995-1996 (Box 33)
      - Invoices, 1987-1992 (Box 34)
      - Banking files, 1995-1996 (Box 35)
      - Banking files, 1995-1996 (Box 36)
      - Banking files, 1996-1997 (Box 37)
      - Operating accounts and payroll records, 1997-1998 (Box 38)
      - Opperating accounts, 1996-1997 (Box 39)
      - Opperating accounts, 1996-1997 (Box 40)
      - Opperating accounts, 1998-1999 (Box 41)
      - Operating accounts and payroll records, 1997-1998 (Box 42)
      - Opperating accounts, 1998-1997 (Box 43)
      - Opperating accounts, 1998-1999 (Box 44)
      - Sales commissions, 1993-1994 (Box 45)
      - Sales commissions, 1993-1998 (Box 46)
      - Banking files, 1999-2000 (Box 47)
      - Banking files, 1999-2000 (Box 48)
      - Banking files, 1998 (Box 49)
      - Invoices, 1993-1997 (Box 50)
      - Invoices, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
      - Tax returns, 1985-1995 (Box 52)
      - Tax returns, 1985-1995 (Box 53)
      - Reports and journals, 1995-1998 (Box 54)
      - Invoices, 1987-1990 (Box 55)
      - Operating accounts, 1996-1997 (Box 56)
      - Operating accounts, 1996-1997 (Box 57)
      - Sales commissions, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
      - Invoices, 1991-1995 (Box 59)
      - Consignment accounts, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
      - Operating accounts, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
      - Operating accounts, 1988-1989 (Box 62)
      - Operating accounts, 1986-1987 (Box 63)
      - Operating accounts, 1986-1987 (Box 64)
      - Auction house accounts, 1988-1998 (Box 65)
      - Sales commissions, 1988-1989 (Box 66)
      - Sales commissions, 1988-1989 (Box 67)
      - Operating accounts, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
      - Operating accounts, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - Invoices, 1997-1998 (Box 70)
      - Banking files, undated (Box 71)
      - Banking files, undated (Box 72)
      - Operating accounts, 1994-1995 (Box 73)
      - Operating accounts, 1993-1994 (Box 74)
      - Sales and commisions, 1990-1998 (Box 75)
      - Banking files, 1988-1992 (Box 76)
      - Banking files, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - Purchasing, 1992-1997 (Box 78)
      - Purchasing, 1992-1997 (Box 79)
      - Operating accounts, 1999-2000 (Box 80)
      - Operating accounts, 1999-2000 (Box 81)
      - Operating accounts, 2001-2002 (Box 82)
      - Banking files, 1997-2001 (Box 83)
      - Banking files, 1997-2001 (Box 84)
      - Banking files, 1997-2001 (Box 85)
      - Accounts, 1995-1996 (Box 86)
      - Accounts, 1980-1989 (Box 87)
      - Accounts, 1980-1989 (Box 88)
      - Accounts, 1980-1989 (Box 89)
      - Payroll, 2000 (Box 90)
      - Artists business files, 1985-1987 (Box 91)
      - Accounts, 1983 (Box 92)
      - Accounts, 1983 (Box 93)
      - Sales and accounts, 1982-1983 (Box 94)
      - Sales and accounts, 1982-1983 (Box 95)
      - Sales and accounts, 1983-1986 (Box 96)
      - Sales and accounts, 1983-1986 (Box 97)
      - Payroll, 2003 (Box 98)
      - Artists consignment files, 1990-1997 (Box 99)
      - Accounts, 1997-2001 (Box 100)
      - Accounts, 1997-2001 (Box 101)
      - Invoices, 1986-1993 (Box 102)
      - Invoices, 1980-1984 (Box 103)
      - Accounts, 1974-1982 (Box 104)
      - Accounts, 1974-1982 (Box 105)
      - Accounts, 1974-1982 (Box 106)
      - Invoices, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
      - Invoices, 1986-1992 (Box 108)
      - Accounts, 1999-2000 (Box 109)
      - Consignments, 1986-1995 (Box 110)
      - Consignments, 1986-1995 (Box 111)
      - Bills, 2000-2001 (Box 112)
      - Payroll, 2001-2002 (Box 113)
      - Operating Accounts, 2003-2004 (Box 114)
      - Leonardo posting journals, 1997-2002 (Box 115)
      - Sales and rolodex, 1986-1987 (Box 116)
      - Sales and rolodex, 1986-1987 (Box 117)
      - Sales and rolodex, 1986-1987 (Box 118)
      - Sales and rolodex, 1986-1987 (Box 119)
      - Sales and rolodex, 1986-1987 (Box 120)
      - Accounts, 1982-1995 (Box 121)
      - Accounts, 1982-1995 (Box 122)
      - Accounts, 1984-1986 (Box 123)
      - Accounts, 1984-1986 (Box 124)
      - Accounts, 1984-1986 (Box 125)
      - Accounts, 2002-2003 (Box 126)
      - Accounts and payroll, 1995-2002 (Box 127)
      - Banking files, 2001-2003 (Box 128)
      - Banking files, 2001-2003 (Box 129)
      - Payroll, 2004-2005 (Box 130)
      - Accounts and travel, 2003-2004 (Box 131)
      - Accounts and travel, 2003-2004 (Box 132)
      - Accounts and travel, 2004-2005 (Box 133)
      - Banking files, 1986-1988 (Box 134)
      - Banking files, 1986-1988 (Box 135)
      - Invoices, 2001-2003 (Box 136)
      - Invoices, 1999-2000 (Box 137)
      - Invoices, 1996-1997 (Box 138)
      - Accounts, 2003-2004 (Box 139)
      - Accounts, 2004-2005 (Box 140)
      - Invoices, 2003-2005 (Box 141)
      - Invoices, 2003-2004 (Box 142)
      - Invoices, 2001-2002 (Box 143)
      - Accounts, undated (Box 144)
      - Accounts, 2005-2006 (Box 145)
      - Banking files, 2005-2008 (Box 146)
      - Banking files, 2005-2008 (Box 147)
      - Banking files, 1998-2005 (Box 148)
      - Banking files, 1998-2005 (Box 149)
      - Payroll, 2006-2008 (Box 150)
      - Payroll, 2009-2011 (Box 151)
      - Credit cards and expenses, 2005-2009 (Box 152)
      - Photoart gift invoices, 2007-2009 (Box 153)
      - Photoart gift invoices, 2007-2008 (Box 154)
      - Invoices, 2005-2007 (Box 155)
      - Bills, 2005-2006 (Box 156)
      - Bills, 2006-2007 (Box 157)
      - Bills, 2007-2008 (Box 158)
      - Bills, 2008-2009 (Box 159)
      - Sales, 1979-1983 (Box 160)
      - Sales, 1979-1983 (Box 161)
      - Sales, 1979-1983 (Box 162)
      - Bookkeeping, 2009-2010 (Box 163)
      - Financial reports, 1996-2005 (Box 164)
      - Bills, accounts receivable, and shipping, 2009-2011 (Box 165)
      - Photoart gifts, 2008-2010 (Box 166)
      - Operating accounts, banking files, and travel, 2007-2010 (Box 167)
      - Invoices, 2006-2007 (Box 168)
      - Invoices, 2006-2007 (Box 169)
      - Invoices, 2009-2010 (Box 170)
      - Banking files, 2003-2005 (Box 171)
      - Business files related to website and computer software, 1995-2005 (Box 172)
      - Vision Gallery inventory, 1986-1996 (Box 173)
      - Liz Kay sales commissions, 1986-1996 (Box 174)
      - Liz Kay sales commissions, 1997-2012 (Box 175)
      - Photoart gift accounts, 2005-2008 (Box 176)
    - Shipping records
      - Shipping records, 2003-2005 (Box 177)
      - Shipping records, 1998-1999 (Box 178)
      - Shipping records, 1998-1999 (Box 179)
      - Shipping records, 1989-1991 (Box 180)
      - Shipping records, 1989-1991 (Box 181)
      - Shipping records, 2001-2003 (Box 182)
      - Shipping records, 1997-1999 (Box 183)
      - Shipping records, 1999-2000 (Box 184)
      - Shipping records, 1998-1999 (Box 185)
      - Shipping records, 1994-1996 (Box 186)
      - Shipping records, 1996-1997 (Box 187)
      - Shipping records, 1992-1994 (Box 188)
      - Shipping records, 1988-1991 (Box 189)
      - Shipping records, 1992-1993 (Box 190)
      - Shipping records, 1996-1997 (Box 191)
      - Shipping records, 2004-2006 (Box 192)
      - Shipping records, 1992-1993 (Box 193)
      - Shipping records, 1990-1992 (Box 194)
      - Shipping records, 2008-2010 (Box 195)
      - Shipping records, 2002-2003 (Box 196)
      - Shipping records, 2000-2002 (Box 197)
      - Shipping records, 2005-2006 (Box 198)
      - Shipping records, 2006-2008 (Box 199)
    - Telephone records
      - Rolodex and phone logs, 1997-1999 (Box 200)
      - Rolodex and phone logs, 1997-1999 (Box 201)
      - Rolodex and phone logs, 1995 (Box 202)
      - Phone logs, 1985-1987 (Box 203)
      - Phone logs, 1985-1987 (Box 204)
      - Phone logs, 1999-2001 (Box 205)
      - Phone logs, 1999-2001 (Box 206)
      - Phone logs, 2000-2010 (Box 207)
      - Phone logs, 2000-2010 (Box 208)
      - Phone logs, 2000-2010 (Box 209)
      - Phone logs, 2000-2010 (Box 210)
    - Stamps and assorted supplies
      - Rubber stamps and office supplies, undated (Box 211)
      - Rubber stamps and office supplies, undated (Box 212)
  - Artist files, Series II
    - Artists files, 1991-2000 (Box 213)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes James Balog, Thomas Barrow, Phil Borges, John Paul Caponigro, Sandra Russell Clark, William Clift, Gus Foster, Lynn Goldsmith, Betty Hahn, Michael Kenna, and David Michael Kennedy.
    - Artists files, 1991-2000 (Box 214)
    - Artists files, 1987-2013 (Box 215)
      Includes David Michael Kennedy, Rolf Koppel, Aruthur Lazar, Herman Leonard, Oscar Lozoya, David Lubbers, Keet McAuley, and Patrick Nagatani.
    - Artists files, 1990-2003 (Box 216)
      Includes D.F. Barry, Chirstina Barthelmess, Bauhaus, E.O.Beaman, Prince Roland Bonaparte, Manuel Alvarez Bravo, Annie Brigman, Charles W. Carter, Henri Cartier-Bresson, Augustin Casasola, Martin Chambi, Walter Chappell, Van Deren Coke, Imogen Cunningham, Joseph Dixon, Alfred Eisenstaedt, Fashion, C.S. Fly, Arnold Genthe, Delancey Gill, Ernst Haas, Phillippe Halsmann, Foreman Hanna, George Hurrell, Irwin (Oklahoma), Andre Kertesz, darius Kinsey, ernest Knee, and J.H. Lartigue.
    - Artists files, 1952-2012 (Box 217)
      Includes Robert Maplethorpe, Percy Harman Marble, Linda McCartney, Lisette Model, Maholy-Nagy, Henry Moore, William Mortenson, Wingate Paine, T. Harmon Parkhurst, Carlo Ponti, Jacob Riis, Wynn Richards, and W. Eugene Smith.
    - Artists files, 1980-1996 (Box 218)
      Includes Jan Saudek, Howard Schatz, Aaron Siskind, W. E. Smith, Alfred Stieglitz, Peter Stackpole, Stroll, Lou Stouman, Karl Struss, Jock Sturgis, and Suta.
    - W. Eugene Smith Files, 1988-1989 (Box 219)
    - Artists files, 1988-1999 (Box 220)
      Includes Bobbe Besold, Rita DeWitt, and Jay Dusard.
    - Artist files, 1986-1992 (Box 221)
      Includes Bernice Abbott, John Adair, Dick Arentz, Frank Armstrong, Bruce Barnbaum, Ray Belcher, Ruth Bernhard, Debra Bloomfield, jim Bones, Edouard Boubat, Robert Bourdeau, Dan Budnik, Harry Callahan, Dean Chamberlain, Walter Chappell, and Judy Chicago.
    - Artist files, 1989-1993 (Box 222)
      Includes Gerald Ackerman, Ansel Adams, Ray Belcher, bobbe Besold, Van Deren Coke, Marianna Cook, Ritat DeWitt, Rick Dingus, Douglas Frank, Robert Frank, W. Von Gloeden, W.H. Jackson, Andre Kertesz, Stuart Kilpper, Karl Koenig, George Platt Lynnes, Tor Maverstrand, Bart parker, Marcy Peck, Rene Pauli, Ted Rice, Ralph Steiner, Clara Sipprell, Paul Strand, and Yazu Susuka.
    - Artist files, 1987-1990s (Box 223)
      Includes Jonathan Clark, Bruce Davidson, Pete Davis, Robert Doineau, Harold Edgerton, Louis Fouree, Tom Feldvebel, Richard Felix, Robert Fichter, Audry Flack, Joan Fontcuberta, Robert Frank, Jack Fulton, Peter Goin, Judith Golden, Herb Green, Goodwin Harding, Chuck Henningson, and David Hockney.
    - Artist files, 1987-1993 (Box 224)
      Includes Henri Cartier Bresson, Bruce Davidson, Jack Delano, Robert Doisneau, Jay Dusard, Laura Gilpin, Kati Horna, Robert Glenn Ketchum, Josef Koudelka, Willis F. "Sonny" Lee, David Lubbers, Danny Lyon, Jim Marshall, elliott McDowell, Helmut Newton, Eliot Porter, Edward Ranney, Ambra Polidori, Ted Rice, O. Winston Link, Karl Struss, Toba Tucker, brett Weston Naef Edward Weston Naef Paula Hocks, Tamara Kaida, Manuel Jiminez, Barbara Kasten, Stuart Klipper, Ted Kuykendall, Bill Lesch, Pedro Meyer, A. J. Meek, Sheila McLaughlin, Jusy Miller, Kenda North, Paige Pinnell, Clarence J. Laughlin, Bill Owens, Mary Peck, Irving Penn, and John Pfahl.
    - Artist files, 1988-1993 (Box 225)
      Includes Robert D'Alessandro, Doug Frank, Rene Pauli, Bart Parker, Mary Peck, Ed Ranney, Ted Rice, Yazu Suzuka, Shiela Metzner, Holly Roberts, Charles Roitz, Meridel Rubenstein, Robin Sachs, Aaron Siskind, Michael Smith, Alice Steinhart, Ruth Thorne-Thompson, Alex Traube, Aruther Tress, Ted Waddell, Lumina photo publishers, Todd Walker, Gary Winogrand, nancy Wood, Joel Peter Witkin, and George Zimbel.
    - Artist files, 1987-1992 (Box 226)
      Includes David Michael Kennedy, Barbara van Cleve, Robert Glenn Ketchum, and Marni Sandweiss.
    - Artist files, 1990-1996 (Box 227)
      Includes Barbara Van Cleve, and Jody Forster.
    - Research notes, 2004 (Box 228)
      Includes Adam Clark Vroman and Lamont files
    - Research notes: PH - T, Lamont Files, 2000-2009 (Box 229)
    - Research notes: W - Z, Lamont files, undated (Box 230)
    - Research notes: W - Z, Lamont files, undated (Box 231)
    - Research notes: K - PF, Lamont files, undated (Box 232)
    - Research notes: D - J, Lamont files, undated (Box 233)
    - Research notes: A - C, Lamont files, undated (Box 234)
    - Research notes, undated (Box 235)
      Includes Christian Barthlemess, Cuba Collection, Charles Lummis, Julian Scott, and Wil Soule.
    - Lamont files, undated (Box 236)
    - Richard Rudisill files, 2000-2010 (Box 237)
    - Lamont files, 2001-2005 (Box 238)
    - Lamont files A - K, 1998-2000 (Box 239)
    - Lamont files L - Z, 1988-2003 (Box 240)
    - Artist files, 1985-1995 (Box 241)
      Includes Gerald Ackerman, Thomas Barrow, Manuel Albarez, Bravo, and Paul Caponigro.
    - Artist files, 1985-1998 (Box 242)
      Includes Paul Caponigro, Henri Cartier Bresson, Van Deren Coke, Edward S. Curtis, Elliott Erwitt, Jody Forster, Lee Friedlander, and Miguel Gandert.
    - Artist files, 1985-1998 (Box 243)
    - Artist files, 1977-1995 (Box 244)
      Includes Betty Hahn, Yosuf Karsh, and David Michael Kennedy.
    - Artist files, 1990-1999 (Box 245)
    - Artist files, 1988-2000 (Box 246)
      Includes Miguel Gandert, Flor Garduno, Kati Horna, Eikoh Hosoe, Magnum show photographers, Millenium Exhibit, Delilah Montoya, Karl Moon, and Patrick Nagatani.
    - Artist files, 2000 (Box 247)
    - Artist files, 1989-1996 (Box 248)
      Includes Patrick Nagatani, arnold Newman, Annie Noggle, Bradley Smith, Andree Tracey, and Barbara Van Cleve.
    - Artist files, 1983-2010 (Box 249)
      Includes Michael Hudock, Annie Leibovitz, David Lubbers, Rolf koppel, and David Michael Kennedy.
    - Artist files, 1985-2000 (Box 250)
      Includes Annie Liebovitz, David Lubbers, Oscar Lozpya, Danny Lyon, Skeet McAuley, and Victor Masayesva Jr.
    - Artist files, 1985-2000 (Box 251)
      Includes Patrick Nagatani, Barabara Van Cleve, John Wawrzonek, William Wegman, Brett Weston, E. Muybridge, and Arnold Genthe.
    - Artist files, 1985-2000 (Box 252)
      Includes Edward S. Curtis, Barbara Van Cleve, Jody Forster, Miguel Gandert, David Michael Kennedy, and Delilah Montoya.
    - Artist files, 1981-1996 (Box 253)
      Includes Jerry Uelsmann, Michelle Vignes, Roman Vishnaic, A. Von dam Busche, Cindy Warwick, Lewis Watts, Wieford Watts, Weegee, Sabine Weiss, Naomi Weissman, Brett Weston, Edward Weston, Gorden Whitten, Leigh Weiner, Anne Wulff, Tom Wolcott, Reid Yalom, and Max Yavno.
    - Artist files, 1993-1995 (Box 254)
      Includes Judy Dater, Robert Dawson, Aubrey Degnan, Tony De Bone, Alma Davenport del la Ronde, Eugenia de Olazabal, Christopher Dierdorff, Frank DiMarco, Margot Duane, Joe Englander, Tom Erikson, Elliott Erwitt, Evercolor printing company, Neil Folberg, Mary Follwood, Oliver Gagliani, Fior Garduno, and Day Carson.
    - Artist files, 1979-1996 (Box 255)
    - Artist files, 1993-1995 (Box 256)
      Includes Richard Nagler, William Neil, Mario Cravo Neto, Nicholas Pauloff, Alfred Palmer, Todd Pickering, Jack Pitonak, Barbara Plowman, Olivia Parker, Jack Radke, Marc Riboud, Irving Penn, Lee Tanner, Lois Tema, Joyce Tennyson, Barbara Traub, Eric Tomberlin, Phillip Trager, George Tice, and Spencer Tunick.
    - Artist files, undated (Box 257)
      Includes Dorothea Lange, Lanscape show, Kristie Laird, Stu Levy, Ken Light, Susan Lipper, Sal Lopes, Ernie Luppi, Mark Lathringer, Salvatore Mancini, Sally Mann, Rosario Mazzae, Jack McDonald, Hansel Meith & Otto Hagel, Ken Miller, Margaret Mitchell, Tom Milea, Joan Murray, Jack Wellpot, E. Muybridge, and Joan Myers.
    - Artist files, 1981-1996 (Box 258)
      Includes William Garnett, Lyle Gomez, Emmet Gowin, James Green, John Gruen, John Hamilton, Loren Hammer, Thomas Harding, Melissa Harris, Steve Harder, Alex Heilmer, Debra Heimendinger, Beatrix Helg, Brenda Hensing, Chuck Henningsen, Lewis Hine, Hollywood, Frank Horvat, Eikoh Hosoe, George Hurrell, Introductions, Graciela Iturbie, Kate Jordahl, Geir Jordahl, William Henry Jackson, Ethan Kaplan, Ira Kaufman, Larry Kennan, Andre Kertesz, Josef Koudelka, Koichiro Iurita, and Vilem Kriz.
    - Artist files, 1990-1996 (Box 259)
      Includes Robert Gueiteman, Clarence Sinclair Bull, Christopher Burkett, Andrew Butler, Moirri Camhi, Paul Caponigro, Don Carson, Keith Carter, Henri Cartier-Bresson, Kevin Cashen, Rick Chapman, Harry Callahan, Robin Chris, Charles Cramer, Tillman Crane, and Imogen Cunningham.
    - Artist files, 1982-1996 (Box 260)
      Includes Bernice Abbott, Don Gregorio Anton, Ansel Adams, Ken Addison, Morley Baer, James balog, Bruce Barnbaum, Chris Barton, Cathy Baum, Sky Bergman, Ruth Bernhard, Laura Blom, Aubrey A. Boding, Edouard Boubat, Manuel Alvarez Bravo, Annie Brigman, Horace Bristol, Barry Beukoff, Kevin Bubriski, and Robert Buetleman.
    - Lamont files, undated (Box 261)
    - Lamont files, undated (Box 262)
    - Lamont files, 1987-2000 (Box 263)
      Includes Chirs Burkett.
    - Lamont files, 1987-2000 (Box 264)
    - Lamont files, 1984-2000 (Box 265)
    - Lamont files, 1984-2000 (Box 266)
    - Artist files, 1984-2000 (Box 267)
    - Gus Foster calendars, 2005-2007 (Box 268 (Broadside))
  - Subject files, Series III
    - Kurt Koegler collection binder American Indian Portraiture, 1991 (Box 269)
    - Art law CLE, Curtis Harriman Alaska expedition, Century of American Indian portraiture, 2005 (Box 270)
    - Fred Currier photograph collection, undated (Box 271)
    - Fred Currier photograph collection, undated (Box 272)
    - Museum of Modern Art 2001, undated (Box 273)
    - Robert Frank collection binders, 1947-1961 (Box 274)
  - Client files, Series IV
    - AIPAD - Cardozo, 1991-2005 (Box 275)
    - AIPAD - Cardozo, 1991-2005 (Box 276)
    - C - D, 1980-2015 (Box 277)
    - E - F (includes Fremont), 1969-2012 (Box 278)
    - F - H, 1981-2015 (Box 279)
    - H - K, circa 2012 (Box 280)
    - K- L, 1980-2010 (Box 281)
    - L - M (Life and Magnum), 1984-2015 (Box 282)
    - Misc - O, 1980-2010 (Box 283)
    - Pa - Ro, 1980-2010 (Box 284)
    - Ro - So, 1980-2010 (Box 285)
    - So - Wirtz, 1980-2010 (Box 286)
    - So - Un, 1984-2015 (Box 287)
    - W - Z, 1988-2015 (Box 288)
    - W - Z, 1988-2015 (Box 289)
    - John Boland, 1987-1992 (Box 290)
    - John Boland, 1987-1992 (Box 291)
    - A - C, 1986-1993 (Box 292)
    - A - C, 1986-1993 (Box 293)
    - A - W, 1987-1993 (Box 294)
    - N - S, 1987-1993 (Box 295)
    - S - Z, 1987-1993 (Box 296)
    - A - L, 1990-1997 (Box 297)
    - A - G, 1989-1998 (Box 298)
    - H - W, 1990-1999 (Box 299)
    - A - F, 1990-1999 (Box 300)
    - G - M, 1989-1995 (Box 301)
    - A - C, 1989-1995 (Box 302)
    - Notes and advertising, 1987-1993 (Box 303)
    - A - Z, 1990-2004 (Box 304)
    - N - Z, 1996-1997 (Box 305)
    - Aspen Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 306)
    - Aspen Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 307)
    - A - E, 1981-1998 (Box 308)
    - E - O, 1989-1999 (Box 309)
    - O - Z, 1980-1997 (Box 310)
    - O - Z, 1980-1997 (Box 311)
    - Miscellaneous files, 1998-2000 (Box 312)
      Includes Austin "Pete" Peterson (Watkins, Muybridge, hart CPRR, son of Harry Peterson, California Librarian for Stanford and others ca. 1900), Jay Frontino (attourney stealing prints from University of New Mexico Library), walter Rosenblum (Paul Messier forensic conservator) lewis Hine fake prints scandal in photo market, c. 2000.
    - Miscellaneous files, 1998-2000 (Box 313)
  - Printed material, Series V
    - Pamphlets and publications, 1963-2005 (Box 314)
    - Pamphlets, 1975-2009 (Box 315)
    - Museum publications, 1990-2010 (Box 316)
    - Magazines, 1955-2008 (Box 317)
    - Magazines, 1950-2010 (Box 318)
    - Magazines, 1950-2010 (Box 319)
    - Magazines, 1960-1999 (Box 320)
    - Magazines, 1914-2011 (Box 321)
    - Magazines, 1914-2011 (Box 322)
    - Magazines, circa 1966 (Box 323)
    - New Mexico publications, 2000-2010 (Box 324)
    - New Mexico publications, 2000-2010 (Box 325)
    - New Mexico publications, 1950-2010 (Box 326)
    - Artists' books, 1962-2008 (Box 327)
    - Artists' books, 1990-1999 (Box 328)
    - W. Eugene Smith, 1944-2000 (Box 329)
    - W. Eugene Smith, 1944-2000 (Box 330)
    - W. Eugene Smith, 1944-2000 (Box 331)
    - Magazines and auction reports, 1960-1969 (Box 332)
    - Technology manuals, 1990-2000 (Box 333)
    - Technology manuals, 1996-1999 (Box 334)
    - Magazines, 1958-1998 (Box 335)
    - Magazines, 1958-1998 (Box 336)
    - Magazines, 1988-1992 (Box 337)
    - Magazines, 1985-1992 (Box 338)
    - Technology manuals, 1993-1997 (Box 339)
    - Technology manuals, 1990-1999 (Box 340)
    - Photo collectors issues, undated (Box 341)
    - New Mexico publications, 1992-2013 (Box 342)
    - New Mexico publications, 1992-2013 (Box 343)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1976-1977 (Box 344)